export const QuizData = [
    {
        "question": "What is PHP?",
        "options": ["A programming language", "A server-side framework", "A database management system", "A markup language"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In PHP, what is the purpose of the 'echo' statement?",
        "options": ["To declare a constant", "To print output to the browser", "To define a function", "To create a loop"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the file extension for PHP files?",
        "options": [".html", ".php", ".js", ".css"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In PHP, how do you declare a variable?",
        "options": ["Using the 'var' keyword", "With the 'let' keyword", "Using the 'variable' keyword", "Simply by using the dollar sign ($)"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What does PHP stand for?",
        "options": ["Personal Hypertext Processor", "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor", "Programming Hypertext Protocol", "Preprocessed Hypertext Pages"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In PHP, how do you connect to a MySQL database?",
        "options": ["Using the 'connect' function", "By including a configuration file", "With the 'mysqli_connect' function", "By setting a global variable"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'foreach' loop in PHP?",
        "options": ["To define a function", "To create a recursive loop", "To iterate over elements in an array", "To execute a block of code a specific number of times"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 'include' statement used for in PHP?",
        "options": ["To include a CSS file", "To insert the content of one PHP file into another", "To declare a constant", "To define a function"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'session_start()' function in PHP?",
        "options": ["To start a new PHP session", "To redirect to another page", "To include external scripts", "To print output to the browser"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In PHP, how do you comment out a single line of code?",
        "options": ["<!-- Comment -->", "// Comment", "# Comment", "/* Comment */"],
        "answer": 2
    }
];